Guide to the Scenic Houston - Scenic Texas Collection 2008-010
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Scenic Texas, 1990-2008
  - Ordinances, Legislation, Policy, Statutes
    - Municipal Regulation Of Signage - Here's Your Sign, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Scenic By-Way Ordinance, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Federal Highway Beautification Acts and Related Issues
    - Highways Beautification Act with Amendments, ctober 22, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Highway Beautification Act - Provisions - Controversy in Texas, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Highway Beautification Act - Provisions - Controversy in Texas, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Highway Beautification Act - Provisions - Controversy in Texas, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Federal Highway Act of 1976 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Billboard Violations, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Definition of "Predominantly Residential Area", 1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Federal Highway Administration, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - National Coalition, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Highway Beautification Program - Annual Statistical Progress Report, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Texas Billboard Control Stats, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Request of Scenic Protection from Roads, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Issues in valuation of outdoor advertising signs, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Press Coverage
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1970s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 5-12)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1997; 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 2000s (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 16-18)
  - Reports and Newlsetters
    - Scenic Byways Bulletin, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Scenic Bulletins, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Texas Certified Cities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Scenic Views, Winter 1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Scenic Views, Winter 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Scenic Views, Summer 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Scenic Texas Documents, 1996-2003 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Publications and Newsletters, 2001-2006 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Scenic Texas Report for 2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Other Scenic Texas Cities
  - Scenic Austin
    - Board of Directors and Committees
      - Minutes - Scenic Austin Board of Directors, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 28-29)
      - Board of Directors, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Board of Directors, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Social Events
      - Billboard Survey, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Reception - Tom Green in Austin, February 1, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Austin Party, November 7, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Scenic Austin Fall Benefit, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Billboards - Ordinances and Press Coverage
      - Austin Tree Ordinance(s) from the Internet, November 2000 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Austin Billboards, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
      - Strengthening Nonprofit Boards, 1991-1992; 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Scenic Dallas
    - Background and Administration
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1995-2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Magazine Articles And Clippings About Billboards, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Scenic Dallas Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Scenic Dallas Income vs. Expenses, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Dallas Information To Michael Collins, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Dallas Work Plan, September 24, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Key Objectives - Scenic Dallas, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Scenic Dallas Info, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors and Committees
      - Zoning Ordinance Advising Committee (ZOAC)/Dallas Planning Commission, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, November 6, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
      - Board of Directors Search, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Illene Perkett - Scenic Dallas Board Meeting, March 19, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Illene Perkett - Scenic Dallas Board Meeting, June 18, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Illene Perkett - Scenic Dallas Board Meeting, October 15, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Ordinances
      - Dallas Sign Code, July 1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Dallas Sign Code, April 20, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Dallas Development Code, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Social Events
      - Dallas Invitations, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Trammell Crow Urban Tree Farm, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Scenic Dallas Event, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Kick Off Reception, September 26, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Reception - Kathy and Harlan Crows Home, May 20, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Scenic Forth Worth
    - Background, Administration, and Press Coverage
      - Mission and History of Scenic Fort Worth, 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Transportation and Public Works, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Scenic Conservation Forum, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Board of Directors and Committees
      - Annual Board Of Directors Meeting - Copy 1, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Annual Board Of Directors Meeting - Copy 2, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Scenic San Antonio
    - Board of Directors and Committees
      - San Antonio Conservation Society, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Minute Book, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Projects and Press Coverage
      - Utility Improvement District, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Kelly Parkway Corridor in San Antonio, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Scenic America/Coalition for Scenic Beauty, 1978
  - Background and Administration
    - Coalition for Scenic Beauty - Brochure, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Coalition for Scenic Beauty - Press Release, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Coalition for Scenic Beauty - Newspaper Clippings, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Coalition for Scenic Beauty - Fundraising Letter, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Affiliate Policy, 1994-2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Email - Summary of the VT Information Study, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - From Sprawl to Smart Growth: How to Achieve Beautiful Results, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Affiliate Agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    - January 30, 2003, January 20, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Billboard and Sign Regulation - Recent Cases and Trends, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Fact Sheets - Billboards and Sign Control, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Brochures, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Scenic Byways, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Scenic Byways Feasibility Analysis, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors and Committees
    - Texas Chapter of Scenic America, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, April 25-26, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, October 31-November 1, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, April 9-11, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, November 13-14, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, April 1-2, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, September 22, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Policies and Politics
    - Sign Control Publications, 1985-1991 (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
    - Survey of State Billboard Control - National Wildlife Federation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - The Aesthetics of Planning APA/PAS Report, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - State Chapter Development, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Sample Bylaws for State Chapters of Scenic America, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Opinion of the General Counsel US Department of Transportation (USDOT), May 21, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Denver - Constitutional Issues, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Texas State Chapter, Charter and Bylaws Draft, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Scenic America, Proposed State Program, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Press Coverage
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1994 (Box 12, Folder 33-34)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Newsletter - Scenic Highways, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Newsletter - Sign Control, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Newspaper Clippings - Scenic Roadways, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Review of Case Law on Constitutionality of Amortization, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Journals, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Trees, Billboards, & the Right to be Seen From the Road, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Takings L.A.W. - In Plain English, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Suburbia's Sights of Stressful Times, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Journal - Gateways: Creating Civic Identity, Winter 1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Letter from Beaufort - Charles F. Floyd, January 1977 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Appraising Outdoor Advertising Signs: A Critical Analysis, July 1998 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - A Drive Through Missouri Should Be More Than Ride Through the Yellow Pages, October 2001 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - A Visit to the Farm - Charlie Floyd, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Mississippi Billboard Valuation Case - Charles F. Floyd, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - The Appraisal of the interests of Outdoor Advertising firms in eminent domain, Charles F. Floyd, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Affiliate Information, 1984-2001 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Photographic and Digital Materials
  - Landscaping slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Garbage slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Billboard slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - No Landscaping slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Good Signs slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Unidentified slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Unidentified negatives, undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Scenic Texas CDs (audio speeches), undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Texas Avenue CDs (photos of brochures - different churches and other landmarks), undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Context Sensitive Signage Design CDs, undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Oversized Materials
  - Green Ribbon Blueprint (Ovs box 13, Item 1)
  - Right of Way Map (Ovs box 13, Item 2)
  - Texas Avenue Interpretive Street Light Bases (Ovs box 13, Item 3)
  - Texas Avenue Light Standard (Ovs box 13, Item 4)
  - Scenic Texas Proposed Scenic Highways (Ovs box 13, Item 5)
  - Exhibit Photos (Ovs box 13, Item 6)
  - Proclamation - Scenic Houston Day (Ovs box 13, Item 7)
  - Certificate - State Of Texas Governor (Ovs box 13, Item 8)
  - Majestic Theatre (Ovs box 13, Item 9)
  - Resolution - State Of Texas (Ovs box 13, Item 10)
  - Texas Avenue Light Standard Base (Ovs box 13, Item 11)
  - Scenic Houston A Campaign For Texas Avenue Historical Markers and Streetscape Improvements (Ovs box 14, Item 1-2)
  - Scenic Houston A Campaign For Texas Avenue Historical Markers and Streetscape Improvements (1 and 2 Combined) (Ovs box 14, Item 3)
  - Former Site of Capitol, Republic Of Texas (Drawer Z.9, Ovs folder 2)
  - Texas Avenue Light Standard Skirt (Drawer Z.9, Ovs folder 3)
  - Site of Church Reserve (Drawer Z.9, Ovs folder 4)
  - Texas Avenue Street Scape Improvements (Drawer Z.9, Ovs folder 5)